Everyone's buying AI stocks, but nobody realizes the real-
Real bottleneck isn't chips or rare earth.
AI data science
centers are power hungry monsters, a single GP.
CPU cluster running AI models can use as much electricity.
as a small town. Right now, US data centers
centers consume about 7 gigawatts of power. And by 20% of the time, the world is still in the world.
In the 2035 they'll need 123 gigawatts.
17x increase in just 10 years.
The problem
help miss you can manufacture chips faster than you can build
power infrastructure. TSMC can expand the fact that
in two years, building new power plants and upgrading the
electrical grid takes 5 to 10 years.
with government approvals.
Companies have been buying old-
power plants and restarting them just to run data centers.
Microsoft is exploring small modular nuclear reactors.
and Amazon is building next to existing power.
stations. This creates a massive opportunity in power
companies that nobody's talking about. US energy provides
are expanding capacity specifically for data centers.
centers.
Infrastructure companies are building the grids to connect
these new power sources. These aren't sexy tech stocks.
They're utility and construction companies, but they're capped.
capturing billions in guaranteed government and corporate contracts.
tracks. The Chips Act gave billions to semiconductor
companies and infrastructure bills are funding grid
modernization. These companies have federal backing and
decade-long demand visibility that most tech stocks
Don't everyone sees the AI chip demand but
If you see the power constraints, that's where the next big offer is.
is hiding in plain sight.