Global liquidity is at all time high. Sounds bullish.
But here's what the headlines miss.
It's not the l-
level that moves markets, it's the momentum.
Picture a plane that's
cruising at 40,000 feet, but the fuel gauge just isn't.
It's empty.
The Altitude is a laggy indicator.
The problem.
The problem has already started, same with liquidity.
Some month rate of change in global liquidity just went negative for the
the first time in years. And here's the kicker, liquidate
leads asset prices by about 90 days.
So the
liquidity that peaked in late 2025. That's Hill with
is fading right now. This might not lead to a market crash.
It might just mean that easy gains are behind us.
The rising.
The maximum liquidity that was supporting assets is starting to receive.
And if Q1 2026 is when this will become awkward.
By then, most people will be asking what happened.
but you'll already know.
Don't miss key insights like this.
I sh-
Share these daily inside of macro pulse.
Comment macro.
to join today.