Almond Kinell Bitcoin, your soldie, my young dollar. Well, have a good day.
(speaking in foreign language)
La was a little bit co-inle million dollar, came to sue people.
I'm not sure if I'm going to be here, but I'm going to be here.
I'm not going to be able to do that. I'm going to be able to do that.
(speaking in foreign language)
I am Al-Fenguahadwershrin, Dhakalala.
to help how Aritha many of whom seem really are good are men and women.
This is a very nice bitcoin, and I will see you in the next video.
I am not a good man, I am a good man.
I'm your friend, I'm your friend, I'm your friend.
I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to get a lot of money.
The hab bhinef sin fattar.
Wuhan nawmun a thalabhijin a bhikkh.
I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to get a good idea.
The first thing I want to do is to make a difference.
(speaking in foreign language)
and in a case for yourself.
I'm not sure if I'm going to do it. I'm not going to do it.
(speaking in foreign language)
The best way to do it is to make a difference.
I'm not going to be able to do that. I'm going to be able to do that.
I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to do it.
(speaking in foreign language)
I will be the owner of the Nefsilfekra.
I'm not going to do it. I'm going to do it.
For Halmungkin and Bitcoin, you also live in Yawn.
I'm not sure. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
(speaking in foreign language)
and the very last one.
Either I should have a good video or the love of Muntavi.
[MUSIC PLAYING]