Which of these assets belongs to this chart?
If you chose to
Silver, you'd be right, and that's exactly why you could be in danger.
Silver is up over 200% since the start of the season.
of 2025. The last time Silver went parabolic like
Like this was 2011.
It hit $48 and collected.
in three months. Before that, 1980.
Silver spike to $50 then crashed 90%.
over two years. Parabolic moves have a perfect
track record. They all end up the same way.
Assets
either need to consolidate into a range or they collapse.
back down. Commodities are intended as long-term holds.
Not momentum trades. Gold has been extended too, but...
that silvers the real outlier right now.
Meanwhile, professional.
investors are already overweighted in commodities. That's
mainstream positioning, which historically marks pops, not bottom.
If you're holding silver, consider taking profits in stages.
The charts screaming exhaustion and parabolic mood.
never end well. I'll show you my full systematic and better
Facing framework for free this Saturday so you can protect your portfolio.
folio from dangers just like this.
Comment, workshop,
and I'll send you the link.
(upbeat music)