What if I told you the strength of the US dollar can tell you?
where the markets are going, let me explain.
US dollar is...
Index, meaning the strength of the dollar, goes down.
global liquidity goes up.
assets like Bitcoin and stocks absolutely ripped.
Think of it like this, imagine the dollar is a giant vacuum.
Cleaner when it's strong it's sucking up all of the money from
around the world, making everything else more expensive and hard.
harder to buy. But when that vacuum cleaner breaks down, when the dog
All are weakens, suddenly money flows freely everywhere out.
Now here's what actually happens a week dollar makes it
Keep your mind on the right side.
companies in Europe, Asia, emerging markets can suddenly affect the economy.
for it to expand, to invest and to take on more risk again.
Plus, all that dollar-denominated debt around the world
becomes easier to pay back.
Less financial stress.
means more appetite for risk.
And here's the kicker.
Since--
It's the start of the year, the US dollar has lost 10% of its power.
while global liquidity rose by over $6 trillion.
That's on a coincidence.
The data shows Bitcoin tipping.
Typically follows this liquidity wave with about a 10 to 12 weeks.
clack. So while everyone's obsessing over fed meetings,
I am watching the dollar index like a hawk. Remember, when...
When dollars get weak, risk gets rewarded.