When Larry Fink, the CEO of BlackRock, says something is
the future, you pay attention. He manages ten.
trillion dollars. That is half the GDP of
China, and he isn't talking about Bitcoin.
talking about tokenization. Let us explain.
Right now, the financial system is running on code written.
in the 1970s.
When you buy a stock, it takes
two days to actually settle.
The market closed
at 4 p.m. and if you want to sell a building
Good luck. That takes months. Think of it like the...
post office before the internet if you wanted to send a
message, he wrote a letter, bought a stamp, and
waited three days. Tokenization is...
is the email moment for finance.
It puts stocks, bonds, even real estate.
on a blockchain. Suddenly that three-day wait becomes
three seconds. But here is where it gets processed.
Once these assets are tokenized,
They don't just sit there.
They become liquid collateral.
Imagine tokenizing your house and using it
to take out a loan in 30 seconds, right on your phone.
without a bank manager in sight.
This is going to ensure
and project trillions of dollars of value into crypto.
And that volume has to go somewhere.
It flows the...
through what we call DeFi that issues the loans.
We are just a random Instagram page, but we're not.
$16 trillion is looking for a home.
we think it pays to know the address.
So hit the
follow.