Bitcoin is retesting its all-time high from 2021.
and it's down about 45% from the cycle peak.
People are terrified, but here's what's really going on.
EVERYONE!
Bitcoin cycle follows the same pattern in 2015.
15, it dropped 86%.
In 2019,
It dropped 84% and in 2022 it just
drop 77% every single time it reco
coverage new all time highs.
And right now, there are two kilos.
levels that professionals watch to identify where Bitcoin tends to be.
the bottom. One is its long-term price trend line.
200-week moving average, sitting at around 50-year-olds.
The other is the average price that every bit goes to be.
The coin holder on the network actually paid.
Sitting around 50 seconds.
6,000 in every prior cycle Bitcoin founded
floor right around where these two lines meet. That doesn't mean
We're at the bottom today, but it means we're entering the zone where
generational buying opportunities have historically formed.
The people who bought during the FTX collapse in 2022.
when it felt like crypto was dead forever, made some of the best
investments of the decade. Bear Markets punish a moat.
and greatly reward patients, but patients without a
system is just guessing when to pull the trigger.
If you want to know more, please subscribe to our channel.
Miss 2022's bottom, this is your second chance.
My upcoming investor workshop shows you exactly what to put.
I went in to buy it and how to position before the next rally.
leave you behind. Comment, rotation for the link to register.
[Music]