What if I told you Bitcoin's most reliable safety net?
just broke. And history says we're not done falling.
Think of Bitcoin's 50-week moving average like a trampoline.
every time Bitcoin fell during this bull run that's
trampoline caught us and bounced us back up until now.
Now, Bitcoin closed below 90k.
through that trampoline for the first time since December 20th.
2021. The last times this happened? 2017.
in 2021, Bitcoin didn't stop at the 50-week.
It felt all the way to the 200-week moving average.
That's currently sitting at about 55k.
Now,
This cycle could be different. We have Black Rock, Micro.
strategy and institutional treasuries buying. But the power of the world is not the best.
is screaming caution. Will institutional investors know that?
help Bitcoin bounce back or is Bitcoin headed toward?
the 200-week moving average. The safety net is broken.
But the question is, how much further do we fall?
If you want to see my breakdown on Bitcoin as it happened, comment.
50 and I'll send you the full video.
[MUSIC PLAYING]