when Larry Fink, Jamie Diamond, and the heads...
of more than 50 firms sign onto the same planet.
And you pay attention.
They are putting 100%
114 trillion dollars of American assets onto the economy.
digital rails. Every share you own.
Every bond you hold, every dollar of treasury.
debt becomes a digital token that moves in seconds.
anywhere on earth. This is not the theory anymore.
The DTCC, the company that
processes $3.7 quadrillion every year.
more than the entire global economy.
Just publish the timeline. July.
the first trades October full launch.
And here is what nobody is telling you.
Every dollar.
of that 114 trillion has to flow.
blow through one of two companies, not 50, not 50.
10.
2.
Think about the American world.
railroads in the 1800s. The country had a
everything except the tracks to connect it.
Some people who got rich were not the farmers.
They were the family.
who owned the rails. Tokenization is the new rail.
railroad. The rails are already built and two companies own the
Think about it. America is about to push the law.
largest pool of capital ever built through two pipes.
The question is whether you read about it next year or un-
understand it now. We covered both names inside the
our research product. We are just a random instagram.
but when 114 people were in the hospital.
trillion picks a road, we think it pays to
know who owns it.