Google Amazon, Meta, Microsoft.
higher AI trade rests on one assumption.
These four hyperscalers must keep their combined 7.
$100 billion in CapEx commitments intact.
Every GPU cluster, every data center, every AI.
semiconductor stock. The entire trade is priced at $1.00.
off that number staying intact or growing.
Building down.
At a center requires shipping massive amounts of equipment.
around the world.
Shipping costs have surged.
You will come.
have also searched and transport disruptions are
ongoing. These companies are facing meaningfully high.
higher input costs than when they made those commitments.
Smart investors don't realize the market isn't pricing
in any risk to that guidance right now. The assumption based on the case of the U.S. government.
into every AI stock you can name is that the cat-vex
holds, rose, and accelerates. That is something...
has never been tested under these macro conditions.
So any CEO speaking about pausing?
delaying or reviewing tapX timelines is a
but how can you see it coming?
You need a system
that never lets you miss a signal.
Comment, blueprint, and I'll see you in the next video.
I'll show you how my system does this for you.
(drum beat)