I'm a very good guy, I'm a good guy, I'm a good guy.
All in the fishi who were Mustak Balalmail, Lazimtintabe.
I'm not sure if you're a lawyer or a lawyer.
and we will see you in the next video.
The first time I've ever seen Bitcoin, it's been a long time since I've been here.
Hello, Nana Shra. Al-An and Nubhamal Māliyām Al-Ai.
the last one.
and the enemy of the enemy, the enemy of the enemy.
I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to do it.
and I will see you in the next video.
The Royal King Actors are a resolable parade, visit them.
I'm not sure. I'm not sure. I'm not sure.
very good.
who will email the Alameh Mel, who will assu-
We send it to the city of Oaxaca.
I'm going to show you a little blockchain.
I am your friend, I am your friend.
I'm going to take a look at this video. I'll see you in the next video.
I will see you in the next video.
liquid collateral. Tachayel in Actorum is based.
of the United States.
I'm not sure if you can. I'm not sure if you can.
The fuck is this? I'm not sure. I'm not sure. I'm not sure.
a leader's door had el corud. Nihana Mujarad Saf had instagram.
Thank you very much.
to the war on Mawa, Nautakudmin al-Hikma.
naktada for learn one. Fadrott mutaba.
(drum beat)