When Warren Buffett spent his last year as CEO selling his
stocks and stockpiling 373.
billion dollars in cash, you should pay attention.
He runs Berkshire Hathaway, the greatest investor.
of all time, and he was doing the opposite of
of what almost everybody else is doing right now.
Let us know.
explain. The S&P 500 is at its
second highest valuation in 145 years.
years, only one period was higher.
.com bubble in 1999.
And here is what almost nobody is pricing in.
For the last 10 years, US companies bought back.
about a trillion dollars of their own stock every year.
year. Imagine a neighborhood where every house
being sold gets demolished.
Fewer houses
More buyers, prices doubled. That is what happened.
to your portfolio. But two things are about to flip.
at the same time. SpaceX is going public this
summer at $1.5 trillion.
Open AI at $1 trillion.
Anthropic.
Databricks, cerebras, the largest equity supply
wave in history, all in 18 months.
same neighborhood. Suddenly hundreds of new houses.
houses on the market.
And here is the part nobody has ever seen.
is talking about.
When SpaceX goes public,
Every passive index fund must mechanically.
buy it. To do that, they sell something else.
else. They sell the legacy companies you already owned.
the new arrival, the buyer that has been holding everything.
up. Gone. Buffett can do math.
soaking you. We are just a random Instagram page.
but when the largest supply wave in history meets the highest.
highest prices in 145 years.
We think it pays to know which side of the table you are on.
Hit that follow.