Stripe Visa MasterCard Paypal
These four companies moved over 20 years ago.
$25 trillion last year.
More than the end.
entire economy of the United States.
They are not
payment companies. They are money movement monopolies.
every time you tap your card, send a watch.
or pay a vendor, one of them takes a cut.
attacks on commerce you pay, whether you notice it.
or not. And that tax is paying for something
absurd. Remember when sending a text message.
cost money, SMS. You paid your
phone company for every message you sent.
then WhatsApp arrived, used the internet instead,
and took a look at the internet.
texting became free. Nobody today would pay for it.
per text it would feel ridiculous.
The system that moves your
money still works like SMS. It passes through
four or five banks before it lands.
Takes two days.
to settle, closes on weekends, and charges a total.
whole at every stop.
Money has not had its worth.
What's that moment yet?
That's why these four companies have...
have been racing to adopt stablecoins.
Last year, stablecoins.
coins settled $33 trillion on the block.
chains, more than Visa and MasterCard combined.
Stripe bought a stablecoin company for over a billion dollars, then
they built their own blockchain and Visa runs a note on it.
MasterCard is buying a stablecoin company of
of their own, and PayPal already issues a stablecoin.
The companies you pay every day are rebuilding the company.
the rails underneath you. Your bank will tell you about it.
in two years. We're telling you now. So follow if you want to
Stay Early.