Peace be upon you, Mr. Haile, and I will see you in the next video.
I am Al Foutes, and I am the President of America.
and the other one.
I'm not sure. I'm not sure.
I am not sure if I am in jail or in the middle of the war.
Mr. Heilnachal Lihat Sir Marathania.
Jadid Il Benkal Fidrali, the Federal Reserve.
Filby Daya can show a lot of the seal. You had it in the special fight.
Baspard Asmet Alphin with her mania, Colshita.
El Fidrali Sarjatbaaflusra kameeja.
I wish that if he has an adaptional bonoque, try it blèche.
Lene.
In the Senate, the President will be able to help you.
and we will see you in the next video.
I'm not sure if I'm going to see you. I'm not sure if I'm going to see you.
Laszimy Staphmer went through hell flows, Lil Assam.
and I will see you in the next video.
Arda'Tla. We'll open the Temlick Assume in Alféno Tisa.
I'm not sure. I'm not sure.
Chufa Nastaritaniu and Tawagavtut Farraj.
(speaking foreign language)
I'm not sure.
and we will see you in the next video.
But the only way to do it is to make it a better life.
our own Aktherm and me at Milliard de la Arbessana.
Thank you for watching, and I'll see you next time.
I am the one who is the most famous, the most famous, the most famous.
It's a very difficult time to get a smile.
I mean, I'll be in the middle of the city of Hillelion, and I'll be in the middle of the city.
at the hub a la car u bet coin you
You are still in the sword, where I have a tofir, wagafmän.
And now, I'm going to take a look at the next video.
I'm not sure. I'm not sure.