All Street and the Homushka Labreem are at the Thalathme Atrelyon.com.
Humble fair, lagwalha taan srahlak, lammat shtir.
I'm a leader, just to be a tough with your mate.
See you at the next time.
or towel flossack with a wand.
Wall Street will hint.
I'm going to say that you're not going to be able to do it.
and we will see you in the next video.
I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to do this.
more animal bitcoin out not that i think tanya best less from i will be
and we will see you in the next video.
Take it up to Daul, Arba where I should install SABAT.
(speaking in foreign language)
We are now at the moment of the pandemic.
Black Rock fee, Harley and Sittmeh at Melion Dollar.
Well, Frankly and Templeton and the home are by me, I think.
I'm going to have a good day. I'm going to have a good day.
of Khathir Reibor ala blukchan Khasvi.
Namo al-Saysat, Ma'ad al-Aqsa.
the Tint of the other. (speaking in foreign language)
I'm going to show you how to make a video. I'm going to show you how to make a video.
I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to do it. I'm going to be able to do it.
and we are going to be able to make a difference.
I will see you in the next video.
(speaking in foreign language)
have the lost soul.
We are going to have a lot of work to do with the economy.
and I will see you in the next video.
(speaking in foreign language)
That's the "How will God is here" and "Tabern"
Thank you.
[MUSIC PLAYING]