To the next episode of Minicrypto, Minicinal Modium, is that...
(speaking in foreign language)
I'm going to ask you to go to Google.
by Namalikriptu, Nasell Hamsawashrum.
with me a thicker tarracal crypto bit by and want to.
I will see you in the next video.
I'm going to show you how to make a video.
For some who had a living, said me and her man in his feet.
The only way to protect the world is to protect the world.
I think that's the only way to get out of the car.
I think it's a good way to get out of the car.
(speaking in foreign language)
The old man is a little bit different.
He is a little bit different.
I'm not sure if I can understand it. I'm not sure if I can understand it.
of the world.
I'm not talking about the way I'm going to be.
the Turkey l'Ekrypto. Relax, be sure in the world. Hualen ala.
and the other one.
(speaking in foreign language)
and I will see you in the next video.
I'm not sure if I'm going to do it.
I will be the first to know you.
Mashro hyper liquid, you weld it for about a million dollars.
of Sena Wian. We stuck them some hour to sein bin mien.
I mean, this year I took a hot bath.
- Yeah, and he beat was so tough.
I am not a man, I am a man.
But the only thing is that the people who are in the field are the people who are in the field.
and the middle of the circle, the circle, the circle.
I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to get a job.
to clear, to mata and har, wut it kara al kal.
I'm your host, Helmand que nocón raltáníne, aquí.
I am not going to be a friend of mine.
I think that we are going to be able to make it easier to make it easier.
was it?