Which of these candles means sell? If you pick this one, you
be right. But there's a lot more that candles can tell you.
First,
Let's break down Candle Anatomy.
The body shows open
and close prices. The top wick shows highest price rates.
reached and the bottom wick shows lowest price hit.
Now, here's the price.
Here's how you read them.
This hammer candle means buyer support.
Christ dropped low, then Beyer stepped in strong.
The shooting star warns of seller pressure.
Price pumped high.
then sellers took control.
Doji candles show complete indices.
Bull's Embairs fought to a draw.
golfing? Yesterday's red candle gets swallowed whole.
Buyers took complete control here.
A bearish engulfing...
works completely the opposite. Today's red candle eats yellow.
yesterday's green and sellers dominated.
So long green
candles seem great, right? Well not always. This could signal
exhaustion if volume drops. Long red candles look like a big deal.
scary, but these panic cells can make great buying on
opportunities. Now spinning tops have small bodies and
long wicks. The market can't decide direction yet.
Evening star pattern, three candles telling one story.
Bulls lost control to the Bears.
about morning sorrow.
reversal. Bears gave way to the Bulls. Most people just chased
screen candles up, but you should really learn to read the stories behind the scenes.
the wicks instead.