2026 could be the worst year of Trump's term.
years wide since 1928 the second year of a president.
His average just 3.3% return.
Compare that to 14% in year 3 and April.
percent in year four. The pattern is consistent regardless of the pattern.
It's a cycle like everything else in market.
Year one, they're delivering on promises.
Year three,
they're pumping the economy to get re-elected.
But year two...
That's when the ugly stuff gets done. Budget cuts, polymers, polymers.
policy fights, the announcements that spook markets.
Traders have tracked this since 1967.
In '90s,
of 16 presidential cycles. Year two was
the worst.
Record lows. Investor exposure is at cycle high.
and sentiment just hit levels not seen since July.
of 2021. The setup is fragile and I bring
Break down how to protect yourself from this every single day inside
at Macropulse. Comment "Macrove" to join.
(upbeat music)