150,000 people lost their jobs to AI.
The biggest companies like Microsoft, Amazon.
and Google are investing $725 billion.
billion into building AI this year.
are pulling that money from payroll.
The CEO of...
of Salesforce cut 4,000 customer support rules.
and said four words. I need less heads.
The fear is obvious, if they can do it.
Who is next?
But the Industrial Revolution
looked exactly like this. 80% of
People worked the land in 1800s, 2% do it.
today. And yet, we are richer than any other.
generation before.
In moments like this, invest
investors sell many of the old winners.
stocks lost over a trillion dollars this year because AI.
made the code itself replaceable overnight.
The investor
that sold are looking for something new. Everyone is
focused on Nvidia and semiconductors, but mark
markets always think about the future, not the present.
Now, investors are asking a different question.
What is growing and immune to AI?
at the same time.
Think about how a market works.
Buyers go where the sellers are, lenders go.
go where the borrowers are.
The biggest pool of money
attracts the next dollar because the biggest pool gives you the best.
price, and every transaction that settles correctly.
is another brick in a wall of trust that takes years.
to build. We call this network effects.
and the specific category is on chain.
finance. Open source businesses where the users are.
are the moat. AI can write the same code.
maybe better, but it cannot replicate the liquidity.
and trust built over 10 years, and it's growing for
faster than anything else.
Stablecoin volume is up.
83% in a year.
Tokenized assets
sets are up nearly 400% in 3.
While software stocks are losing a trillion, this can...
category is doubling every 12 months.
If you want to see more of this video,
see where on-chain finance is going, Lincoln Bio.