Everyone hates inflation through groceries cost more gas
cost more, rent cost more, but here's what nobody told me.
tells you, the Federal Reserve would rather have 10%
inflation, then 2% deflation.
Dromed Powell's
literally has nightmares about falling crisis. Japan expects
have experienced deflation for 20 years. Their stock market still has a lot of money.
recovered from 1989. Think of deflation like a
The store announcing prices will drop 5% every week.
Nobody buys today because next week is cheaper but wouldn't
Nobody buys the store drops prices 10%.
Now everyone.
Everyone waits even longer, and the store goes bankrupt.
This creates a death spiral.
Businesses can't sell products.
to the fire workers.
is fall further and the waiting game intensifies.
Venezuela had 130,000% inflation and
recovered, Japan had 2% deflation and lost
three decades. This is why the Fed printed $5 trillion.
in 2020. They'll destroy your dollars to save the system.
Bitcoin protects you from this.
They'll always choose inflation over the next few months.
over deflation so only asset they can't print.