Peace be upon you, I am not afraid.
to Aktherm in Trillion on us for the Lord. We shall all end.
I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to do it.
I'm not going to be able to do it.
I'm not sure if you're a good man.
I'm not sure if I'm wrong, but I'm not wrong.
and I will see you in the next video.
and I will see you in the next video!
I'm not sure if I'm going to get a good one.
defer. Like in a several hakariquil official alpha.
who are in the Sukh was al-Sakhf.
and naturally by the Oubili crypto, or of our segments.
Sir, will more societal kibira cannot mum know?
and we will be able to see it.
I will see you soon.
But the last thing I want to say is that it's not a lie.
and we will see you in the next video.
I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to do it.
and we will see you in a minute.
I'm not sure. I'm not sure. I'm not sure.
I'm not sure if I can get it. I'm not sure if I can get it.
We are now at the bottom of the mountain.
We will take the right hand and the right hand.
And now we have a new idea. We have to go to the gym.
and we will see you in the next video.
I'll see you in the next video.
But sir the methyl-Ayaml-internet-l-oolah, you're...
and I will see you in the next video.
on the Internet.
We are now on the internet, we are going to talk about the internet.
Sisko and Harat will top the codmital Amazon.
or goggle, he'll say it out of the hall. When you have to...
I'm not sure if you have any questions.
A.V. or Uniswap.
Tintage the same with me, huh?
the Holy Spirit.
the man who has been here.
and we will see you in the next video.
[MUSIC PLAYING]