Wall Street has a cheat code. It's called the carry trade and
right now is falling apart.
For decades, investors are
borrowed Japanese yen at near zero interest rates and it
invested that money in assets worldwide.
Stocks?
crypto commodities, anything with better returns than there's
0% interest, trillions of dollars in leverage.
positions built on cheap yen funding.
known as the carry trade.
And when the yen strengthens suddenly,
those traits unwind violently.
When the Bank of Japan...
raise their rates for the second time in a decade in August.
2024, the following crash erased 6.0.
$4 trillion from the markets overnight.
On September 19th, the Bank of Japan raised their interest.
rates to the highest level in 30 years.
So far,
This third hike hasn't triggered chaos. Why?
Because the Yen is still weak against the dollar and carries it.
trades are still profitable.
But Japan's already said
More rate hikes are coming in 2026.
If the dollar beacons for any reason while Japan keeps it.
hiking, the Yen search is fast.
And when the Yen search is fast.
the carry trades unwind.
That's the Blackbird.
one nobody's watching. I'm breaking down even
more hidden risks on January 24th in my 2026.
6. Investor Dilemma Workshop, the factors that move market
but never make headlines until it's too late.
Comme!
Comment 2026 below and I'll send you the link to join.
(upbeat music)